wandisco.com 2018-09-11

# Privacy Policy | WANdisco

**Privacy statement and summary**

Thank you for visiting WANdisco.com. Your privacy is important to us. To protect your privacy and help you to make informed choices, we provide this notice explaining our information practices, how you can choose how we use your data, and your rights in relation to your data.

In brief, we will only use your information:

·       to provide services that you or your organisation have requested; or

·       where you have consented to us doing so.

This is explained in more detail below.

We do not routinely sell or licence your personal data to anybody, and we only use your personal data as described in this Privacy Notice.

**About us**

This site is operated by WANdisco, Inc., WANdisco International Ltd and WANdisco, PLC. (each and together, " **WANdisco** "). We are jointly headquartered in the US and the UK:

**US HQ**

5000 Executive Parkway

Suite 270

San Ramon

CA 94583

T +1 925 380 1728

F +1 866 247 7584

| 

**UK HQ**

Electric Works 

Sheffield Digital Campus 

Sheffield 

S1 2BJ

T +44 114 3039985

---|---  

For the purpose of the UK Data Protection Act 1998, we are registered as a data controller with the UK Information Commissioner's Office under registration number Z3043345.

**The information we collect and how we use it**

·       **Personal information you provide to us**

(a)    When you have requested services

You may provide us with your information when you order products or services; enter contests; vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion; subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters; download our binaries from our website, request a free trial of our products, fill in a form on our website, or participate in an online forum or community. You may also provide us with information about yourself if you correspond or otherwise interact with us on behalf of an organization.

We will use this information in order to fulfill your (or your organization's) requests for our products and services, and to respond to your inquiries. To this extent, we process your information in the performance of the contract between us and as part of our general business operations. If you do not provide us with the necessary personal data, we may not be able to provide the requested services to you and/or your organisation.

(b)   Marketing and advertising

We will only process your information in order to offer you other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

You can choose to unsubscribe from our marketing emails at any time by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of the email, or by emailing us at [marketing@wandisco.com](mailto:marketing@wandisco.com). If you do so, we will not send you any more marketing messages, although the messages we sent you prior to unsubscribing will still be lawful.

·       **Information provided to us by your organization**

If we provide services to your organization, your organization may send us information about you. This may include information such as your name, work address, e-mail address, job title, telephone number, fax number and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. We will use this information in order to provide the services we have agreed with your organization.

We will process this information in order to perform the contract agreed between us and your organization. It is also important for us to have sufficient information to perform our services and administer our business effectively. 

·       **Information that we collect automatically**

We may collect certain information automatically when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).  We use this automatically-collected information to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We may also use this information in the aggregate (i.e. in a way that does not identify you) to analyze site usage.

Many of our web pages use 'cookies'. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), and save your password in password-protected areas.

We use the following cookies:

Google tag manager

We also use our own cookies from [wandisco.com](http://wandisco.com/), or [svnforum.org](http://svnforum.org/) (and hadoop-forum / gitforums ) to facilitate login etc. 

We process this automatically-collected information because it is in our interests as a business to make sure that our website functions smoothly and effectively. If you reject our site's cookies, or have turned cookies off in your browser, you will still be able to use the site, but you may find that the site does not function optimally or that certain aspects of its functionality are impaired. 

**Communications about our services**

If you have registered an account with us (either on your own behalf or on behalf of an organization), we may use your personal data to provide you with certain communications such as service announcements and administrative messages. These communications are considered part of the services that you (or your organization) have requested from us and you cannot opt out of these emails. 

**Disclosing information to third parties**

**Service providers**

We will share your personal information with our trusted third party service providers where we need to do so in order to provide you (our your organization) with the services you have requested, or where necessary for our legitimate business administration purposes. Such third parties include our payment processor; the company that provides our client record management tools; our mailing list administration software; and our lead management service provider.

**In accordance with the law**

On rare occasions, we may release personal data when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law, regulation or legal request; to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of WANdisco, our employees, our users, or others. 

**Business transfers**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. If WANdisco or substantially all of its assets were acquired (such as through a merger or acquisition), or in the unlikely event that WANdisco goes out of business or enters bankruptcy or is dissolved or otherwise reorganised, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. In any of these events, we consider that it would be in the legitimate interests of WANdisco (or our creditors or transferee(s)) that the relevant customer information be transferred.

**Data storage, security and transmission**

Agents and contractors of WANdisco who have access to personal information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for WANdisco.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data, and unauthorised entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

**Third party websites**

Our site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Please consult all third party sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, third parties.

**Children**

We do not knowingly market or provide our services to children, and our services (including this website) are not designed for use by persons under 18 years old. Children under 18 are not allowed to register with or use our services, or to submit personal data to us. If we discover that we have collected personal information from a child under 18, we will delete that information as soon as reasonably possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a person under age 18, please contact us at [marketing@wandisco.com](mailto:marketing@wandisco.com).

**Your rights**

You have certain rights over your personal data. You may:

·       require us to rectify the personal data we hold about you, where that data is incorrect;

·       require that we restrict the processing of your personal information in certain circumstances;

·       request access to the personal data that we hold about you;

·       require that, in certain circumstances, we delete the personal information we hold about you;

·       require that we provide you with the information that we hold about you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format;

·       withdraw your consent to our using your data for marketing purposes at any time; and/or

·       lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority .

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [[privacy@wandisco.com](mailto:privacy@wandisco.com)], or by writing to us at:

Privacy and Legal  
4847 Hopyard Road, Suite 4-208  
Pleasanton, CA 94588, USA 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@wandisco.com](mailto:privacy@wandisco.com).
